Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see?
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand,
cut through the wind and make A stand,
don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone,
we'll go where we all want to go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
Be fire!
Stop moving!
Are you just going to
shoot lasers at me all day?
I won't stop till I get enough!
That rapid-fire laser crap is a real pain.
Franky would love to
get his hands on that.
I'll kill you!
Final check.
No turning back. Just do it.
Have another babe come on
it's gonna get ugly and curly
brows can't handle this fight
on his own he doesn't have an
ounce of fear that settles it
prepare the injection Miyagi
the patient has given us
informed consent you may proceed
Hey, too deep, too deep!
Oh, I'm sorry.
The bandages are terribly
thick, of course,
so I just have to guess
where your bane is at.
Then get them off me!
I suppose that would make more
sense, but we've come this far.
What kind of doctor are you?
Uh...
Uh... Ah!
Ah!
Whoa!
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ah!
Huh?
Leave the small fries to us!
You just worry about Sasaki.
You got this, iron bro!
Oh, you guys came back to lend
little old me a hand! Yeah!
Hey, Armored Division!
I know you're being controlled by someone
right now, but it's still a mutiny,
and that's punishable by death!
Sam, I thought I was kicking ass,
but you don't have one scratch.
Stubborn, ain't you?
Same goes for you, so I'm
going to give you a choice.
You can back off.
Or you can die right here!
As it turns out, our subordinates on
the performance floor have all defected!
So I'm done wasting time!
I'm gonna go butcher all those traitors!
You are one of us.
Here is where you belong.
I raised you to protect the land
of Wado in my stead, Yamato.
Is that what you think
a good father would do?
You were a bad child for
eating that Devil Fruit.
I worked hard for that, and
it wasn't intended for you.
It's your fault I was starving to
death you think I was happy I want
to go out to sea and Now I can't
even swim again and again I've tried
and failed to finish you off but
every time you Struck me down I've
come back stronger do you know what's
kept me on this island it wasn't
Those handcuffs I'm staying here to
fight for the freedom of this country.
I Mustn't falter.
For I am Odin!
I'm gonna tear straight through you. Oh,
yeah Is your man-beast
form that strong you
want to see watch close
cuz this will be quick
I'm going to use a spruce sword!
You think your little
twirling sword scares me?
I am moving an inch, huh?
You got this, iron bro!
And we got your back!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
What's wrong?
Come on!
You're done for!
Yes, I got this.
Again, step back.
Why don't you go help anyone else?
But if you want them out of the way,
I'll be more than happy to help you.
I don't have any allies
anymore, so I can let loose.
Whoa, it's Finn?
That's crazy, bro.
He's a triceracopter!
Dyrus was ruined!
Damn straight!
Guys, this is bad news!
I'm a dangerous iron pro!
Run for it!
You bunch of morons!
Worry about yourselves
if you don't wanna die!
Hell is there a sign!
Run away!
Didn't think he could fly!
I gotta change my strategy, and quick!
General Blood!
They don't teach this in science books,
but this is the Triceratops' power!
They really undersold you guys.
What's he doing?
Does he get a charge?
Okay, ready!
Come at me, bro!
General Shield!
You kidding me?
Did this guy forget how propellers work?
He must have had it
spinning the wrong way.
Hey, if you turn it clockwise,
you're gonna go in reverse.
Man, this is awkward.
Do I...
do I gotta tell him how
his own body operates?
Secured runway, as planned.
You liar!
Oh, shut up!
A longer charge makes for
a stronger charge, right?
Real talk, General Shield.
You better not let me down.
Pull it, Triderotron!
Oh, great.
He's about to stop his rockets.
They're gonna blow.
You're done, boss.
Oh, yeah?
How about this?
General...
SUPLY!!!
Please don't die!
You gotta get up!
You can do it!
Dammit!
Where's the captain when you meet him?
His lungs have been cleared, right?
I don't think there's anything
else we can do for him.
The captain would give him some medicine.
No an injection he's so pale you
can't die wake up what do we do?
He's breathing again thank goodness!
Your skin is as tough as armor,
and if that cut on your belly is
any sign, you're not invincible.
This should do it.
Franken-sword!
Be for victory, Blast!
Maybe don't advertise
it next time, you idiot!
I'm not exactly super when
it comes to sword fights.
Looks like I'm going to have to bust
out my super duper final finisher.
Are you scared?
Well, you should be!
Oh, crap.
If I keep going this way, I'm gonna
lead him to the performance floor.
I gotta make my stand here and
down before it gets any closer.
Well, let's try the cops!
I'm ready to rock!
Go on, Cannon!
Portable version!
General Cannon!
You can't defeat the Toby Robo!
We strike fear into the hearts
of all who face us, damn it!
I'll take you down with
me, Magnus Saratons!
Lost and loaded.
Thank you, Chronicle B!
The dog-dog fruit, mythical type.
Your model is Okichi no Makumi.
It is a treasure you have stolen.
You've become Wano's guardian deity.
Absurd to think that my
treasure was eaten by
someone who calls himself
Odin but it doesn't Have to
be a mistake protect Rain
for me be its guardian
deity just like I asked you
to No that's a sick joke
Orochi has a talent for
exploitation I'll give him that much
He made this whole
country a weapons factory
You have plenty of slaves
here The bent here will easily
I am Kozuki Oden
And I shall open the borders of Wano
I vow to set everyone free
Not just the samurai But all the people of
Wano Will join the world
after all these years?
Blast friends!
Now we can't wait for fun!
I'll end your dreams right now!
What's this?
Oh, I fear this is no ordinary fog.
Robin!
You sure have grown up.
It seems like you've become a fine
archaeologist, Robin. I'm proud.
Mother?
Yes.
Come here.
Give your mother a hug.
Don't do it, Robin!
Illusion Mist.
Full of sweet memories to tear
you apart from the inside.
What's wrong, Robin? Come here.
We're all waiting for you.
None of this is real.
You think I wouldn't know.
Though it is enticing.
This illusion is a mirror, after all.
A mirror that reflects my childish heart.
Still, my friends are fighting
for their lives right now.
This is hardly time to reminisce.
I have a job to do.
Forget about your friends.
You're coming with us now.
Pathetic.
Saw would never say such a thing.
History is a treasure.
Mankind's guiding light.
Illuminating us all.
It's not some illusion that
you wouldn't understand.
Tres Moon!
Fresh!
You'll regret this.
The illusion didn't work!
How did she see through it?
Come on.
Hurry! Catch her!
You really had me worried
back there, Robin.
Could have given me a heads up that
you were onto there, but, you know.
Thank you for your concern, Brooke.
I appreciate it.
But I could never lose to someone who
would dare use my memories against me.
Truly despicable.
Impossible!
The illusionist should work on everyone!
How did they just waltz right through it?
Why, Nico, I'm surprised at you. Huh?
I never imagined you'd be your own mother.
What a horrible woman you are.
Go away, spider!
This place is way too scary for me!
And I'm a corpse!
You managed to see
through the illusions too?
Oh, yes.
That said, they were quite cruel.
But I'm used to that.
I was trapped in that mist for 50 years,
wishing I would wake up from my
nightmare and find my friends alive.
When you see visions like that every
day, you learn to live with pain.
You know, I think you and
I have a lot in common.
I'm just glad we both found our way here.
Run, Yudo!
Sleeve-swing!
She's using that wheel's weapon again!
There's no escape!
I'm actually shocked you two
didn't fall from my illusions.
After all, you're clearly
living in a dream world.
If you think you could ever be Kaido.
Spider, no!
Thanks for that, Robin.
The entire floor is on fire!
What do you think you're
accomplishing here?
You're going to burn
down the whole castle!
You're worried about our castle?
How sweet of you.
In that case, why don't you
be a good girl and surrender?
Could you keep holding on to me
for a moment, if you'd be so kind?
Seems that weapon is a living thing.
I can work with that.
Cold soul.
I hope you don't mind, but
I don't do well in the heat.
This calls for a soul break.
Ice burn.
You just don't know when to quit, do you?
Give it up, Nico Robin.
It's time to wake up.
Your friend sold you out so that he could
escape, and then he left you here to die.
Blackleg knew you were my target, but he
still called for you when I asked him to.
It's no surprise.
The strongest pirates in the
world all have their eyes on you.
And that's turned you into a
liability to your crewmates.
Blackleg couldn't wait to get rid of you.
Help me, Robin!
Help me, please!
And now he's the laughing
stock of the whole island.
Pathetic worm.
His bounty's rather high.
Second highest in your crew, right?
That doesn't reflect too
well on the rest of you.
Oh, that's Sanji.
He sure is something else.
All right.
Robin, shall I leave this
particular foe to you?
I'm glad you asked.
That sounds lovely.
Good because these
ladies need my attention.
If you'll excuse me.
I have a bone to pick with them.
Did I hurt your feelings?
Not at all.
Sanji is kinder than you think.
You don't need to understand
why he asked for my help
and you don't need to know
how much that means to me.
But you should know when the
new king of the pirates soars,
he'll be one of his wings.
I'll end this, Pigante Blur!
Someone's angry.
That certainly is an impressive
trick you've pulled out.
But it looks exhausting.
No need to worry.
It'll all be over before you know it.
Now, sea serpent!
Snap dragon!
You stay right there.
Too slow!
What?
Did you think I'd just stand
here and let you beat me?
So hitting these arms
hurts your real body, huh?
You've turned yourself into
such a nice big target.
So much to jump.
I hardly know where to start.
Light, wouldn't you see?
Those are poison bars.
Maria Knight!
More meat, more meat, hurry!
Better give him what he wants.
He's already eaten all the
provisions on the ship.
Yeah, and have you noticed where we are?
Because I don't think
they have a butcher shop.
Luffy!
Mama, how did your crew find Luffy Taro?
He fell into the sea. I know.
We saw him sinking and
picked him up in our sub.
Ufiyu, you really did survive.
So glad you're still here.
What happened to you?
You fall down too?
Yes, or rather we escaped.
Shinobu flew us here.
But I periled titans.
Kiku and Kin'emon, they helped us play.
They protected us.
Master King
You always do this.
Save it for later.
You're the leader of the troops.
Don't cry yet.
We have a battle to win.
We gotta beat Kaido.
No crying until then.
That is enough.
Talking to him like that
is only making it worse.
Show us a backbone.
Be brave.
You're gonna be Shogun someday.
I can't move! I'm hungry!
Give me some meat!
Let's all stop yelling
and look for some more!
Hurry! Hurry!
Huh? Huh?
Is that Straw Hat?
Looks like he's at death's door!
This is bad.
Really bad what's going to happen to me if
he dies i didn't account
for this in my plan!
I'm gonna be stuck in
this hell whole country
without a friend in sight
i need him to survive!
This hey
mama i'm gonna
need you to take me
back to Onigashima turn
into a dragon fly me up
Take me to Kaido.
I'll do the rest.